Hi, I'm Tim.
I've actually had to use him twice this year already for,
uh, my wife's car, fortunately.
But Ed's a great guy. They're great people here.
The car came back beautiful each time.
The first go around there was an issue with one
of the parts that was defective.
He had no problem taking it back
and got it back to me the same day.
Fixed. They're good people and they care about what they do.
I've known 'em since they moved in here.
They've really turned the place around.
It looks great inside and out.
The people that work here haven't met one I don't like yet.
They're just good people, good genuine people.
It's an unfortunate circumstance to have to come
to a place like this, but if you have to,
Phil's is the place to go.
I've had no issues. My insurance company loves them.
Yeah, state Farm, they, they love using 'em
because they know they're gonna do a quality job at a fair
price.